Guide to the Brooklyn, N.Y., Department of Law, Corporation Counsel records 2013.015
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 1: Case Files, 1849-1920; 98.0 linear feet; in 199 manuscripts boxes, 4 flat boxes and 1 flat file drawer
  - Steingotter, Philip, and Frank Bennett, as executors of Margaretha Koerner - Assessment dispute, 1898 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    North 6th St. and Roebling St.
  - Steinhart, Louis and William H. Stausser, as assignees of Henry Brau, 1898 (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Stern, Joseph, as assignee of John S. Leach - Long Island City services, 1898 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Sternfels, Samuel M., as assignee - Long Island City engineer salary, 1898 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - Steuhardt, Lewis, 1898 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Stiefel, Henry - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - Stiff, George - James R. Marston clerk salary, 1898 (Box 125, Folder 23)
  - Strong, Benjamin G. - Borough Coroners dispute, 1898 (Box 125, Folder 24)
  - Stuber, Edward - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Sutton - Assessment dispute, circa 1898 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Swanson, August, as Administrator of Martin Lawson - Death by electric shock by a wire, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Tait, Harold - Long Island City services, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Tate, Augustus C. - Inspector of Customs, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Tate, Augustus C. - Water Registrar dismissal, 1898-1899 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Thompson, George - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Thorn, Abia B. - Accountant dismissal, 1898-1899 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    See also Weeks, Joseph S., Abia B. Thorn, and James H. Baker - Accountant dismissals, 1897-1899
  - Townsend, James R. and Henry E. Coe, as Executors of the estate of Charles A. Coe - City Magistrates Court lease, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    Corner of Butler St. and Court St.
  - Tyrrell, Edward B. and others - Long Island City services, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Tyrrell, Edward M. - Long Island City services, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Union Free School Number 3, Town of Castleton - Foreclosure, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    See also Castleton - Map of District No. 1, circa 1898 (Property series - Outside Brooklyn subseries)
  - Van Nostrand, Charles - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Various claim cards, 1898 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Village of College Point against Anton Rausch, Philip Lebkeucher and Helene Brede and City of New York against Joseph Strauss and others (1 of 2), 1898-1901 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    Water superintendent bonds
  - Village of College Point against Anton Rausch, Philip Lebkeucher and Helene Brede and City of New York against Joseph Strauss and others (2 of 2), 1898-1901 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Walton, E. F. - Petition for water main, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    Situated on Goodrich St., between Potter Ave. and Woolsey Ave. in the First Ward of the Borough of Queens (present-day Astoria)
  - Walz, Louis - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Ward, Neil A. - Assessment dispute, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    Ward 5 - Block 27 - Lot 23 (Sands St., between Gold St. and Hudson Ave.)
  - Warnke, Henry - West 8th St. and Neptune Ave. rent, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Washburn, William A. - Long Island City Board of Education compensation, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Weeks, Joseph S. - Accountant Dismissal, 1898-1899 (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Weismantle, August - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Wells and Newton Company - Brooklyn Disciplinary School for Boys work contract, 1898-1899 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - West, George E. - Registrar dismissal, 1898-1899 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    Regarding civil service appointments during the consolidation of Brooklyn with the City of New York; Includes Brooklyn Department of Health records used as evidence
  - White, Robert - Bridge repair contract dispute, 1898-1899 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Whiting, Fernando T. - Police force dismissal, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Wibelitz, Charles - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Wilde, Mary E. - 9 South Oxford St. assessment dispute, 1898 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Wilkes, Daniel W. - Coal delivery contract dispute, 1898-1899 (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - William F. Clark and Company against M. Gibbons and Son - Kings County Hospital labor lien, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Williams, Percy D. and Thomas Adams, Jr. - Bergen Beach fence dispute, 1898-1899 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Williams, Thomas - Police salary, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Willis, Joseph D. - Rent, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    Corner of Court St. and State Street
  - Wilson, James B. (Company) - Long Island City Board of Education contract dispute, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Wischman, Herman - Tax cancellation, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    Ward 25 - Block 16 - Lots 173-176 (Block bound by Patchen Ave., Lafayette Ave., Van Buren St., and Reid Ave. (now Malcolm X Blvd.)); See also Rudolph, Ida - Tax cancellation, 1898
  - Wood, Anna E. - 413 Adelphi St. property damage, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Wood, Nathaniel - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Woodruff, H. B. L. - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Woodruff, Harlow - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Wooster, Edwin P., as assignee for Charles Beuthorn - Ash removal contract, 1898-1899 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Wyeth, John - City Hall boiler repairs, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Yaretsky, Emmanuel M., as assignee - Long Island City street services, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Young, John G. - Bond and Warrant Clerk dismissal, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    See also Squire, Frank H. - Bond and Warrant Clerk dismissal, 1898
  - Young Men's Christian Association - Water rate dispute, 1898 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    Ward 3 - Block 21 - Lot 36 (Baltic St., between 4th Ave. and 5th Ave.)
  - Zier, William G. - Barbey St. injury (1 of 2), 1898-1901 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    Folder (2 of 2) is located in oversized box 238
  - Zier, William G. - Barbey St. injury (2 of 2), 1898- 1901 (Box 238, Folder -)
    Survey of south east corner of Barbey St. and Pitkin Ave.
  - Zimmerman, William - County jail discharge, 1898 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - A. P. Smith Manufacturing Company - Department of City Works services, 1899-1900 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Albro J. Newton Company - Lumber and materials furnished, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - American Lucol Company - Department of Parks paint, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Baldwin, Thomas S., 1899 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Bamberger, Ira Leo - Legal services (1 of 2), 1899-1901 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Bamberger, Ira Leo - Legal services (2 of 2), 1899-1901 (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Bates, Johanna E. - Prospect Ave. assessment refund, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Berger, John J. - Water meter inspector dismissal, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Blank, Joseph - Street lighting contract, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Bridges, Joseph - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Brooklyn Children's Aid Society - Water rates, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn and Jamaica Bay Turnpike Company - Agreement to cross conduit for water supply, 1899 (Box 238, Folder -)
    Includes diagram showing crossing of trolley railway over conduit and pipes east of Spring Creek Pumping Station
  - Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company - Application for release of bond, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company - Brooklyn railroad franchises and fees, 1899 (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company - Permit to construct double track railroad on East New York Ave. (1 of 2), 1899 (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Brooklyn Heights Railroad Company - Permit to construct double track railroad on East New York Ave. (2 of 2), 1899 (Cabinet Map Room - Flat Maps cabinet, Drawer C3)
    Map showing franchise on East New York Ave. from Fulton St. to old city line
  - Brooklyn newspapers, 1899-1901 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    Including The Brooklyn Daily Eagle, The Brooklyn Daily Times, and Roehr Publishing Company
  - Brown, Charles O. - Consulting engineer services, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Brown, Reuben - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Browning, J. Hull - Grant St. grading assessment refund, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    Grant St. is now known as Snyder Ave.
  - Burke, Edward K. - Book binding services, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Butler, Stephen - Boatman dismissal, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Campbell, Michael G. - Carriage repairs, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Cantillon, Daniel J. - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Carey, James F. - Flatlands surveying services, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Carey, John B. - Stenographer's services, 1899-1900 (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Carpenter, William O. - Axman salary, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Chase, Edwin H. and others - Public School No. 4 payroll, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 12)
  - Church of Our Father - Tax cancellation, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    Lefferts Pl. and Grand Ave.
  - Cisco, Elizabeth against the School Board of the Borough of Queens, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Clark, Elizabeth A. - Nurse services, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Clark, James - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - Clark, John - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 17)
  - Cline, Catharine - Tax cancellation, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 18)
  - Cloonen, Mary A., as administratrix of William H. Cloonen - Brooklyn Disciplinary Training School food services, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 19)
  - Cody, Richard J., William J., and James A. - Paving contract dispute, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 20)
    Cody Brothers
  - Coney Island and Brooklyn Railroad Company, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 21)
  - County of Nassau - Division of the property the County of Queens, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 22)
    Dispute arising from the consolidation of the City of New York and the creation of the County of Nassau; See also County of Queens, 1898- 1900
  - Covert, Abraham D., 1899 (Box 130, Folder 23)
  - Cowenhoven, John - Justice of the Peace of the County of Kings services, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 24)
  - Crooks, Robert H. - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 25)
  - Cunningham, George - Department of Sewers services, 1899 (Box 130, Folder 26)
  - Dacey, James against Brooklyn Disciplinary Training School, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Dady, Michael J. - Roa Hook gravel, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Delehanty, William H. and George H. Smyth - Fire Department salaries, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Donlon, Peter - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Doyle, Albert - Columbia St. horse and wagon injury, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Duryea, Mary Bowne - Petition to cancel void tax sale, circa 1899 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Echelsbach, Jennie - Senior nurse salary, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - Eiselstein, George - Parks Department work, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Ellett, James T. against Joseph O'Grady and others (Supervisors of Richmond County), 1899 (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Ellis, Mary - Smith St. sidewalk injury, 1899- 1901 (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Ellsworth, Sanford J. and others - Public School No. 39 payroll, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Ennis, Thomas L. - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Farrell, Patrick - Paving contract, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Ferguson, William - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Finch, William Y. - Night medical services, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Finnigan, Michael E. - Commissioner of Estimate salary, 1899-1901 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Flynn, James - Sealer of Weights and Measures salary, 1899-1900 (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Ford, Michael - Sealer of Weights and Measures salary, 1899-1900 (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Galling, John Joseph - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Gerrity, Thomas J. - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Gerzky, Michael and Betsey - Petition for an order allowing the adoption of a child under twelve years of age, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 21)
    RESTRICTED
  - Gibbons, Richard - Precint Station House alterations, 1899 (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Gillan, Michael - Horse services, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Gray, John M. - Ballot recount, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Gray, Wallace V. - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Greene, Frank L. and others - Public School No. 9 payroll, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Grozinger, Christian and Charles Trautmann - 195 Hamburg Ave. sewer property damage, 1899-1901 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Gulick, Almira F. R. - Gates Ave. sidewalk injury, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - H… [?], George - Police force complaint, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    Last name illegible
  - Hart, John H. - Janitor salary, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Hebenstreit, Henry - 369 Knickerbocker Ave. sewer property damage, 1899-1900 (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Heddenberg, Peter J., 1899 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Hegeman, Catharine against William Lynch and others - Foreclosure, 1899-1900 (Box 132, Folder 11)
    31st St. and 4th Ave.
  - Hickey, Maurice F. - Street services, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Hinchcliff, William J. - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Hines, Charles - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Hirst, Ellen - 134 Underhill Ave. water main property damage, 1899 (Box 132, Folder 15)
    Or Helen
  - Hoffman, Nicholas, Jr. - 190 Stanhope St. sewer property damage, 1899-1904 (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Hogan, Mary - Buffalo Ave. injury, 1899-1901 (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Houstoun, Andrew M. - Board of Education contract dispute, 1899 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Hunter, Charles - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Hunwick, William - Wallabout Market laborer salary, 1899-1901 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Hyde, E. Francis and William Alvin Bartlett, as executors of Samuel B. Duryea - Ocean Parkway assessment, 1899 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Immaculate Inception Nursery - Water rates, 1899 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    117 Sands St.
  - James H. English and Son, and the Tower Manufacturing and Novelty Company, 1899 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - James Ryan and Company - Headstone erections, 1899 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Jappe, Peter and Henry Koster - 383 Knickerbocker Ave. sewer property damage, 1899-1900 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Jennings, Charles J. and others - Public Schools No. 47, 48, 49 and 50 payrolls, 1899 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Jensen, A. Lawrence - Legal expenses, 1899 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Julig, Charles F. and William J. - 692 Humboldt St. sewer property damage (1 fo 2), 1899-1901 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Julig, Charles F. and William J. - 692 Humboldt St. sewer property damage (2 of 2), 1899-1901 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Kaminester, Herman and others - Sewer property damage, 1899- 1900 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    Or Kaminister; 184 Stanhope St., 396 Knickerbocker Ave., 468 Marcy Ave., and 478 Marcy Ave.
  - Karjalainen, John - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Kavanagh, Owen J., 1899 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Kelly, John - Horseshoeing services, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Includes memorandum book
  - Kelly, John - Police force dispute, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Kelly, Martin - Snow removal services, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Kennedy, James H. (Editor, Hardware) - St. Nicholas Pl. snow removal, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Kenney, Mary - Sackett St. sidewalk injury, 1899-1901 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Kessler, William J. - Sealer of Weights and Measures salary, 1899-1900 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Ketcham, Herbert T. - Assessment Commissioner services, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Kings County Elevated Railroad Company - Assessment dispute, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Kings County Elevated Railroad Company - Tickets issued and redeemeed by the Police Department, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Kings County Gas and Illuminating Company - New Utrecht bill, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Knittle, Albert - Recover cash from police, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Koch, John - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Lane, Charles E. - Engineer salary, 1899-1900 (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - Langston, Ralph E.- Sealer of Weights and Measures salary, 1899-1900 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Leach, Charles - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Linden, Frank V. - Clock services, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Lloyd, Alfred - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Long Island Water Supply Company - Town of New Lots water bill, 1899-1900 (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Low, William E. - Parks Department laborer salary, 1899-1901 (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Luff, Charles A. - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Lyons, Marie E., Eliza A. Lyons, and J. P. Bullwinkle - Land condemnation judgement, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    5th Ave. and 67th St.
  - Macauley, Richard J. - Glass services, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Maguire, Richard and Anna - Petition for an order allowing the adoption of a child under twelve years of age, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - Manger, Veronika, administratrix of John Manger - Middagh St. death, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Marlon, Shuckland, Sears, Rosch (?), 1899 (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Martin, William - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - Maynard, George - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - McBride, Maria - Randall's Island Hospital nurse services, 1899-1900 (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - McCormick, John - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - McClunn, William P. - Clerk salary, 1899-1900 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - McCluskey, James P., 1899 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - McDermott, John J. - Wallabout Market paving contract, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - McGarry, Joseph - Police Clerk audit, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - McHench, Mary J. - Principal salary, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    See also Townsend, Jeremiah - Principal salary, 1899
  - McHugh, Patrick - Assessment dispute, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    Ward 17 - Block 175 - Lot 1 (Norman Ave. and Humboldt St. (southwest corner))
  - McLaughlin, James W. - Long Island City patrolman salary, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - McMullen, Jane - 575 Gates Ave. sidewalk injury, 1899-1901 (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - McNamara, John J. - Department of Sewers groundsman salary, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Meares, Richard - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Meehan, Denis - Counsel fees, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Miller, George W., 1899 (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Richard - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Miller, William - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Mittnacht, Henrietta A. and E. Hastings - Fire proof safe sale, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 16)
    Mittnacht's Eagle Safe Company
  - Montfort, Frank K. and others - Public School No. 31 payroll, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 17)
  - Moran, William - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 18)
  - Murphy, Edward - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 19)
  - Munz, M. Frank - 431 Knickerbocker Ave. sewer property damage, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 20)
  - Murphy, John - Counsel fees, 1899 (Box 136, Folder 21)
  - National Wall Paper Company - Water rate dispute, 1899-1900 (Box 136, Folder 22)
    Ward 8 (all): Block 37 - Lots 35-38 (3rd Ave. and 24th St.); Block 59 - Lots 17, 35-38 (3rd Ave. and 35th St.)
  - Nelson, Peter J. T. - Boiler engineer services, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Nelson, Samuel - Assessment dispute, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Neu, Edward - Abandonment, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - New York Association for Improving the Condition of the Poor - Assessment dispute, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Newdecker, Joseph - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Nicholas Gas Fixture Manufacturing Company - Contract dispute, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Night medical services (various), 1899 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Nill, Jacob - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - O'Brien, Michael - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - O'Connor, Thomas - Abandonment, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - O'Rourke, J., Jr. - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - O'Sullivan, John D. - Department of Highways Inspector dismissal, 1899-1900 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Otis Brothers and Company - City Hall elevators contract dispute, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - P. Ballantine and Sons - Foreclosure, 1899-1900 (Box 137, Folder 14)
    Hicks St., near Coles St.
  - P. Kane Harness Manufacturing Company - Stabble supplies, 1899 (Box 137, Folder 15)
  - Palmer, A. Emerson - Secretary of the Board of Education removal (1 of 2), 1899-1900 (Box 137, Folder 16)
  - Palmer, A. Emerson - Secretary of the Board of Education removal (2 of 2), 1899-1900 (Box 137, Folder 17)
  - Parry, Frank H. - Horse and wagon services, 1899 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Paton, Henry - Prospect Ave. assessment refund, 1899 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Patterson, William H. - Freeport property damage, 1899-1900 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Peckham, William C. - Meteorological services, 1899 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Peirson, M. A. - Assessment refund, 1899 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    Ward 29 - Block 68 - Lot 4 (Prospect Ave. and Vanderbilt St.)
  - Peverelly, Augustus - Bicycle injury, 1899- 1902 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    336 Hudson St., Manhattan
  - Pierce, John W. - Physician services, 1899-1901 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Post, John D. - Inspector of Baths salary, 1899 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Quintard, John A. - Department of Charities and Corrections counsel dismissal, 1899- 1902 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - R. F. Stevens Company against Lawrence J. Collins - Judgement debtor, 1899 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Reilly, John F. - Stenographer dismissal, 1899-1900 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Reynolds, William H. - East Side Park Lands assessment, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Roman Catholic Church of Our Lady of Angels - Tax cancellation, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Roman Catholic Orphan Asylum Society - Assessment dispute, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    Located at Park Pl., between Albany Ave. and Troy Ave.
  - Rossa, O'Donovan - Inspector of Weights and Measures salary, 1899 -1904 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Roundtree, William - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - St. John's Hospital, Long Island City - Water rates, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - St. Martha's Sanitarium and Dispensary - Water rates, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    950 St. Marks Ave.
  - St. Michael's Protestant Episcopal Church of Brooklyn - Tax cancellation, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Schafhaus, Bertha, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Schirmer, William C. - Medical Inspector dismissal, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Schluchtner, Herman - Hardware and house furnishing goods, 1899-1900 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Schneider, John - 342 Knickerbocker Ave. sewer property damage, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Scholl, Anton - Wagon repairs, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Scholl, Catherine and Jacob - 33 Morrell St. sidewalk injury, 1899-1901 (Box 139, Folder 14)
    Morrell St. ran from Debevoise St. to Maujer St.
  - Schwan, John - Village of Arverne-by-the-Sea street cleaning, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Sheehan, Thomas - County jail discharge, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Short, Mary Elizabeth - Assessment refund, 1899-1901 (Box 139, Folder 17)
    Ward 29 - Block 398 - Lots 48 and 56 (Grant St. (now Snyder Ave.), between Lott St. and Prospect St.; and Lott St., between Erasmus St. and Grant St.)
  - Simpson, Owen - Brooklyn Bridge horse death, 1899 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Charles F., John Drescher, Jr., and George Rebhan - Wallabout Market lease disputes, 1899-1900 (Box 139, Folder 19)
    City of New York against Smith, Drescher, and Rebhan
  - Smith, William E. - Inspector of Weights and Measures salary, 1899-1900 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Southard, David R. - Freeport property damage, 1899-1900 (Box 139, Folder 21)